Where is he?
It's uh
5:58 in the morning. There he is.
There he is.
How you doing, man?
>> [laughter]
>> So, [music] did you sleep at all?
Congratulations.
>> [music]
>> There are a number of well-placed
clean public toilets in New York City.
Right now, Dan is taking advantage of
one such public bathroom.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, people.
All right, Dan.
>> [music]
>> Been a pleasure.
>> It was a nice run, my friend.
>> Thanks for the miles.
>> See you, buddy.
>> Godspeed.
So,
9 miles at an 8:26 pace, and that was
today is day 697
of running every day. 697 days with no
days off.
Coming up on 2 years.
>> [music]
>> We've got a situation.
Oh, I'm just taking pictures of the
cops.
Okay.
>> Okay?
>> Sorry.
Crime scene.
They connect cheese, salt, pepper,
ketchup.
Yogurt.
Yo.
>> [laughter]
>> Bacon, egg, and cheese, salt, pepper,
ketchup is delicious, but yogurt is
healthy.
Bacon, egg, cheese, salt, pepper,
ketchup is delicious. Yogurt is uh
>> [music]
>> Morning, Bobby.
>> Morning.
>> Hey, how are you, brother?
Long time.
>> Long I saw you yesterday.
>> Yesterday? I told you it wasn't Muhammad
yesterday.
>> No, I was here yesterday.
>> Chef, please. I'm going to make it a
bacon, egg, and cheese on a roll, salt,
pepper, ketchup.
>> Part of being adult is not having anyone
to tell you what you should and
shouldn't eat, which is both an asset
and a liability.
People send me letters, like not all the
time, but people send me letters.
Sending an email is so easy. You have to
respect the hustle of when somebody
takes the time to send you a letter.
From 2012 to 2018, I kept and cataloged
every letter that everyone ever sent me.
That's what's in these binders. I don't
know why I stopped. I think it just got
to be like too much paperwork.
Dear Casey Neistat, I appreciate the
formality. I just wanted to start by
saying I've been a huge fan of yours. I
appreciate that. I wanted to do a
project with you for years. So, I
appreciate the letter and sure, I'd be
happy to make a video with you sometime.
I don't know, Ethan, if you're like 8
years old or you just have the
handwriting of an 8-year-old. Either
way, that's cool, but if you are
a little kid, then like let's get your
parents involved too, but thank you for
the letter. Dear Casey,
love the colors. I receive a lot of
messages after all you've been a huge
part of my husband's life. Sending a
birthday card, if it ever makes it to
your desk, [music] could you write a
short note for my husband? Woman sent me
a note asking me to send her a birthday
card for her husband, which I didn't get
in time. I won't make it to him in time,
but she gave me her cell phone number.
This is a total stranger.
>> Hello?
>> Hello, is this Apurva?
>> Yes.
>> Hi Apurva, this is Casey Neistat
calling. You sent me a letter.
>> Yes, Casey.
>> I have bad news, which is I just got
your letter, so I'm not going to send
your note back in time for your husband
to get it for his birthday tomorrow, but
the good news is I'm making a video and
I'll post it tomorrow, and I'll make
sure I wish him happy birthday in the
video. Is that cool?
>> Thank you so much, Casey. I cannot tell
you how I happy I am to receive this
call.
>> [music]
>> Champagne party popper.
Happy birthday, Gurav.
Yo, all right, lunch?
All right, you coming down?
Okay.
You want a party popper?
>> [music]
[music]
>> This one.
Can I have the seven, please?
>> Number seven, [music] spicy?
>> Extra spicy, extra jalapenos on there.
>> Extra spicy, extra you. All righty.
I know I was like a superstar right now.
What the
Excuse my language.
You should have told me. Now I'm hyped.
Now I'm hyped.
Brian didn't know I had a YouTube
channel.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Pleasure. Brian.
>> Pleasure.
>> Appreciate it.
>> Got it.
>> Saigon Restaurant in Little Italy.
My highest endorsement. Don't sue me if
you fall, all right?
You got to hold
You just don't push it so hard. You know
what I mean? [laughter]
There you go. You got to keep your
weight forward. Now roll it back it'll
slow you down. Roll the wheel back.
Casey. Casey Nakai.
>> Nakai.
>> How fast can it go?
>> 25.
>> Geez.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's been so long since making videos
was the main like the primary focus of
my career.
And I have all these like wonderful
fantastic responsibilities now that fall
outside of just making videos. Making
videos is something I do when I can
instead of it being the main like
thrust.
And I had like a particularly like just
consuming day yesterday. I was talking
to my friend and he was like, "You need
to make something." So last night I went
home and like before I left the office I
brought my point and shoot home with me
and I was like, "No matter what, I'm
going to I'm going to start something
today
and finish it." And this is whatever,
finished enough. It's fine.
But I have to say that process is
cathartic.
It is like
>> [sighs]
>> to finish something, and it makes me
think like
one, how did I how did I do this every
day?
And then two, like, I remember that
feeling of finishing something every
day. I mean, it mostly destroyed every
other aspect of my life when I was
making a video every single day, but
that part of my life, like the
the creator, the maker part of my life
was so fully satiated then.
I may not make more of these. All right.
Uh happy birthday to um
happy birthday.
>> [music]